GUSTAVE HABIMANA

End User Support

Passionate IT professional with over two years of experience in web development and information technology infrastructures. I have the ability to adapt as a self-starter as well as work in collaborative environments to produce results that align with business goals.

Work History

2021-05 -Current

End User Support

ETRADE, Alpharetta, GA

- Identifies and resolves incidents/requests and logs all interactions
- Evaluates and resolves work orders and requests regarding use of application software or hardware
- Creates and configures user accounts in Active
 Directory for new users, and disabling old accounts
 when needed
- Manages user accounts, security and distribution groups as needed for users
- Grants permissions and configures hardware for new employees as part of onboarding process
- Installs, modifies and repairs software and hardware to resolve technical issues

2019-05 -2021-04

Junior Web Developer

Denwize LLC, Atlanta, GA

- Built application using JavaScript DOM for better UI and used CSS3 for styling
- Developed and maintained React components of application
- Implemented JSX, and DOM for content rendering, and handling user Events
- Implemented Axios Asynchrony RESTful API for data request while maintaining application functionality
- Utilizes GitHub for source code management and for version control
- Implements React lifecycles for better user

Contact

Address

Atlanta, GA, 30328

Phone

7707447139

E-mail

ahabiman@icloud.com

WWW

gustavehabimana.com

Skills

Application development

Application support

Project Management

JavaScript

Software Development

Testing and maintenance

Amazon Web Services (AWS) Integration

Contiguous integration systems

Front-end frameworks

UI/UX

interaction, and app rendering

- Operated with tools like NPM, source control Git, and Visual Studio for deploying and editing codes, and bug fixing
- Deploys applications using Netlify and AWS Amplify for CI/CD

2014-09 - Customer Relations Manager

Penske Automotive, Buford, GA

- Communicated effectively as liaison between clients and other department employees
- Developed solutions for service automating by analyzing, and addressing client's problems
- Created healthy fast-paced, and agile environment through team building activities and training

Education

2020-01

2010-01 - B.A: Political Science

2016-12 Georgia Gwinnett College - Lawrenceville, GA